New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides Records
1908-2002
1988-1995
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap151
84.27 cubic ft.
Records of non-profit citizens' organization committed to reducing hazardous chemical pesticides use through education and advocacy.
Administrative History
In 1989, Tracy Frisch, an etymologist who had suffered from pesticide poisoning, formed a non-profit citizens' organization called the New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides (NYCAP). Its mission was primarily to reduce the use of hazardous chemical pesticides through education and advocacy ["NYCAP", Series 1, Box 2, Folder 32].
The early issues that NYCAP championed included the following: safe pest control for schools, hospitals, and public places; reducing work exposure to chemicals; farm worker protection; prevention of groundwater pollution; environmentally sound farming; and strict regulation of pesticides. NYCAP also sought to provide leadership on these issues to other organizations such as parent teacher associations, labor unions, and general environmental groups. To achieve these goals, two major projects were set up: the School Campaign and the Occupational Health and Workers Rights Projects. Both sought to develop legislation on pesticide alternatives and educate farmers on sustainable agriculture ["NYCAP Welcomes You!" NYCAP News, vol. 1, no. 1 (1989), p. 1, Series 6, Box 3, Folder 29].
One of the organization's first activities was to publish NYCAP News, a quarterly newsletter that contained personal stories of members, legislative news, information on pesticide issues, the newest staff and organization news, and upcoming events. The publication was small in the beginning but grew to over thirty pages. It eventually changed its name to Solutions with the spring 1996 issue.
In accomplishing its mission, conferences, workshops, training courses, and a mail order clearinghouse were used to spread information on subjects such as school and workplace integrated pest management, household pest control, organic farming and gardening, multiple chemical sensitivity, workers' rights, and sustainable agriculture ["NYCAP", Series 1, Box 2, Folder 32]. These programs extended all over New York State, with similar conferences held in the Capital Region, Western New York, Long Island, and Central New York. NYCAP was known for its work on integrated pest management, participation in the Negotiated Rulemaking Committee on Safe Housing, as well as its commitment to spreading awareness of multiple chemical sensitivity.
Tracy Frisch was the first executive director and editor of the newsletter, staying with NYCAP until mid-1995 [NYCAP News, vol. 5, no. 3 (1995), p. 2, Series 6, Box 3, Folder 31]. Marilyn DuBois served as interim director until James Moore took over in late 1995 [Correspondence, Series 1, Box 1, Folder 33]. Pamela Hadad-Hurst succeeded Moore and remained executive director until the organization's demise in 2003.
NYCAP's primary area of service was the east coast, but it did have membership nationwide [Gabrielle Blake. New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides, (NYCAP) (online). Troy, N.Y.: Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (9 March 2004) Available from the World Wide Web (http://www.rpi.edu/
interns/work/internships/Environment/NYCAP.html) (File Not Found 20 February 2006)]. By 2003, NYCAP was run by a staff of three people, an executive director, an information director, and a staff person at the Western New York branch of NYCAP that opened in May 2002 [New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides. WNY Region (online). Albany, N.Y.: New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides (10 March 2004) Available from the World Wide Web (http://www.altpest.org/) (File Not Found prior to 20 February 2006)]. NYCAP was governed by a Board of Directors, and a Steering Committee made up of members of other environmental groups, both national and regional [NYCAP News, vol. 1, no. 3 (1990), p. 2, Series 6, Box 3, Folder 29].
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the activities of the New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides (NYCAP) from its creation in 1989 through its demise in 2003. The organization was formed as a not-for-profit group devoted to educating the public about pesticides and other environmental dangers. It was able to spread its message through conferences, workshops, mail order catalogs, information requests, school programs, and contributions to policy-making.
The collection consists of administrative files such as committee and meeting minutes, fundraising campaigns, by-laws, correspondence, annual telemarketing campaigns, grant proposals and funding, invoices, prepaid sales receipts, and technical assistance logs. Mailing and membership lists for NYCAP and some related organizations are also included in this collection, along with state and national legislation; government reports and publications; conference planning, programs, and attendance lists; information requests, news clippings and journal articles on pesticide-related topics; pesticide fact sheets; brochures and pamphlets; pesticide labels; and copies of newsletters, magazines, journals, and other publications of related groups received through a newsletter exchange. The collection also includes numerous videotapes, audiotapes, photographs, slides, computer media, posters, and artifacts.
This collection documents the professional career of Tracy Frisch in the decade before her founding of NYCAP. Material from her career as a New York State Legislature lobbyist and staff member is included, as well as materials from her research on environmental pests and pollution during the 1980s.
Strengths of the collection include the the collection of the publications from many local, state, and some national organizations, along with the collection of information on pesticides and pests from about 1980 to 2000, and the prominent subseries in the Issue Files Series, particularly Agriculture and Lawn, Health Issues from Pesticide / Chemical Use, and School / IPM. Other strengths include the conference material and the membership and mailing lists, which document the first fourteen years of NYCAP.
Arrangement of the Collection
Divided into 7 file series, some with numerous topical subseries.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides in December 2002, January 2003, and February 2003.
Related Materials
See also the following collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives: the Malcolm Willison Papers (APAP-055), which contains notes received from NYCAP concerning an environmental science class Willison taught at Siena College in 1991-1992; Environmental Advocates of New York Records (APAP-104), which include files on NYCAP activities; the Citizens' Environmental Coalition (APAP 197); and other collections available from the Conservation and the Environment subject page.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Pesticides -- Environmental aspects -- Measurement.; Environmental health -- New York (State).; Environmental health -- Political aspects -- New York (State).; Environmental policy -- Social aspects -- New York (State).; Organic farming -- New York (State).; Water quality -- New York (State).; Multiple chemical sensitivity -- New York (State).; Pesticides -- New York (State).; Pesticides -- Government policy.; Environmentalism -- New York (State).; Minutes.; Administrative records.; Membership lists.; Publications, serial.; Business letters.; By-laws (administrative records); Newsletters.; Agriculture; Albany, New York; Medicine and Health Care; Conservation and the Environment; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Frisch, Tracy.; New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides.
- Administrative Files, 1980-2002; 1; 11 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records from the New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides and local organizations that are members of NYCAP, or that relate to the staff (particularly Tracy Frisch) directly. It includes the following: committee meeting minutes, agendas, and reports; fundraising activities; annual telemarketing campaign call sheets; by-laws; correspondence; New York State Department of Labor grants; donation receipts; health insurance information; information request letters; technical assistance logs; and prepaid sales and invoice receipts from 1997-2002, [which provide almost the only information on the organization from that time period in terms of membership, information requests, donations, conferences, and sales].
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - 1 in 9/ NYCAP Ad Campaign, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - "1 in 9" Symposium, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - About NYCAP, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Action Guide For Source Water Funding, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Adirondacks- Activist List, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Administrative Notes on Conferences, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Advertising in NYCAP Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Advertising/Marketing, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Advisory Board, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Advocacy, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Agreement with Buckley, Gent, MacDonald, and Cary, Certified Public Accountants, 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Albany County Pesticide Sunset Ordinance, Training Manual, 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Albany-Municipal NTPM Contact, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Albany NTPM- Educational Information for Building Occupants, 1989; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - America's Charities Application, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Ann R. Roberts/Fund of the Four Directions, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Another Way to be Green Grant, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Annual Campaign, Telemarketing Script, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Annual Membership Drive, Notes, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, Photocopy and Floppy Disk, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - ARISE Foundation Anti-Pollution Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Attorney General Funding for NYCAP Projects, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Audit Contracts, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Audit, FYE, 1995 June 30 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Baltimore Woods Project/Tierra Farm, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Beldon Fund, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Ben and Jerry's Foundation, 1998-2002 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Benefits, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Bishop, David. Suffolk County Legislator, Correspondence on Proposed Pesticide Legislation, 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Black Locust Tree Infestation- Pine Bush, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Board Biographies, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Board Candidates, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors Election Ballots, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - BOCES Outreach/ New York State Department of Labor Grant, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Boards of Cooperative Educational Services, (BOCES) Programs, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Board- Generic Committee Information, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Board Invitees, Information Packet, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Board Invitees, 1995-2001 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Board Meeting, 1996 April 21 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Board Meeting, 1996 July 21 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Board Meeting, 1996 October 20 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Board Meeting, 1997 January 11 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Board Meeting, 1997 May 3 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Board Meeting, 1997 July 19 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Board Meeting, 1997 September 20 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 January 17 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 April 21 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 July 21 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 August 25 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 November 14 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - Board Meeting, 1999 February 27 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 51)
  - Board Meeting, 1999 April 28 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 52)
  - Board Meeting, 1999 July 14 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 53)
  - Board Meeting, 1999 December 9 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 54)
  - Board Meeting, 2000 April 13 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 55)
  - Board Meeting (1 of 2), 2000 September 12 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 56)
  - Board Meeting (2 of 2), 2000 September 12 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 57)
  - Board Meeting, 2000 December 5 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 58)
  - Board Meeting, 2001 April 4 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 59)
  - Board Meeting, 2001 October 10 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 60)
  - Board Meeting, 2001 December 5 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 61)
  - Board Meeting, 2002 March 13 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 62)
  - Board Meeting, 2002 September 18 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 63)
  - Board Meeting/ Common Council Meeting, 1998 December (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 64)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 65)
  - Board Meeting Minutes (June 10) and Dissenting Letter about them by One Member, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 66)
  - Board Member List, 2002 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 67)
  - Board Member Training, Recruitment, and other information, 1990-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 68)
  - Board News/ "The NYCAP Board", 1996 November (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 69)
  - Board of Directors- Composition, September 30 Meeting Minutes, and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 70)
  - Board of Directors- General Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 71)
  - Board Retreat, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 72)
  - Brethren Volunteer Service, Church of the Brethren, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 73)
  - Brochures and Mailers, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 74)
  - Brochures, Flyers, and Related Notes- NYCAP and others, ca. 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 75)
  - Budget (October 1997)/ Check Signing Ballots (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Budget 2002, 2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1994 July-1995 June (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Budgets, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Budgets, 1995-1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Budgets, Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Buffalo- Activist List, Clippings, Etc., 1990-1993 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Bylaws for NYCAP, 1990-1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Campaign for Human Development, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Capital District Lawn Campaign, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Capital District Injured Workers Meeting Announcements and Planning, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, Background Information, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Chemical Hypersensitivity Syndrome Study Review Committee, Excerpts, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Chemical Sensitivity Support Group and Injured Workers Support Group Meeting Report, Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Chemically Related Illness Research, Public Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Cisco Systems Stock, 1999 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Citizens Clearing House for Hazardous Waste (CCHW), 1989-1993 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Citizens Clearing House for Hazardous Waste (CCHW), 1994-1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Citizens' Environmental Coalition VEATCH Grant Proposal, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - City of Albany Neighborhood Associations Contact Lists, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Comic Strip on MCS, by Treesha De France, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Community Foundation for Greater Buffalo, 2002 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Community IPM Coordinating Council, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Computer Database and Internet Source of Interest to NYCAP, 1989-1997 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Conference Request Letters, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Conference Sponsorship and Budgets, Miscellaneous, 1993; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Cornell IPM- Community IPM, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Cornell Partnering, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Board of Directors, 1996; 1999 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Positive Member Feedback, 1997-2002 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, School Pesticide Monitor, 2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1995-1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Log, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1986; 1989-1992 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Correspondence with SUNY Institutions, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Council of Community Services, Member List and Annual Report, 1992-1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - Cottonwood Foundation, 1990; 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Council of Community Services/National Society of Fund Raising Executives, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - C.S. Fund, 1989; 2002 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - C.S. Fund/Warsh-Mott Legacy, 2002 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - Database Information, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 51)
  - DEC Buffalo Planning, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 52)
  - DEC NTPM Allocations (Financial Records), 2000-2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 53)
  - DEC Outreach on IPM, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 54)
  - DEC/Westchester County Planning, 2000 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 55)
  - Department of Labor, Grant Budget, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 56)
  - Department of Labor, Grant Contract and Forms, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 57)
  - Department of Labor, Grant Correspondence, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 58)
  - Department of Labor, Grant Proposal for 1994, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 59)
  - Department of Labor, Grant Proposal for 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 60)
  - Department of Taxation Pesticide Incident Reports, 1982; 1985-1987; 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 61)
  - Department of Labor Fund, General Ledger, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 62)
  - DOL Newsletter Distribution, ca. 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 63)
  - Donations of Office Supplies, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 64)
  - Donations to NYCAP, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 65)
  - Donor Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 66)
  - Dubois, Marilyn M., Transition Memos, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 67)
  - Entango/ENN Affiliation, Online Donation Services, 2000 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 68)
  - Environmental Federation of New York, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 69)
  - Environmental Health Working Group Conference Call, 1999 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 70)
  - Environmental Support Center, 1992-1994 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Environmental Support Center, 1994-2001 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Environmental Support Center- Apple Computer Donation Program, 1994 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - EPA Environmental Education Grant, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Ephemera, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Events Planner, Correspondence and Brochure, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Farmworker Justice (1 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Farmworker Justice (2 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Farmworker Justice (3 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Financial Information, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Financial Mistakes and Corrections, 1997-2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements and Audit, FYE, 1994 June 30 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements, FYE, 1995 June 30 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements, FYE, 1996 June 30 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Fishgold Gunther- Workplan and Agreement, Meeting Summaries, Progress Reports, 1995 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Flyer Samples, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Formation of NYCAP and Business Start-Up, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)